{
    "subject": "Arthur_Rankin",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "_Jr. The_Last_Unicorn__film_",
    "human_readable": "Arthur Rankin directed the film _The Last Unicorn_.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9181265234947205,
            "question": "Can you name other films directed by Arthur Rankin besides _The Last Unicorn_?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8883281350135803,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Arthur Rankin."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.882398247718811,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Arthur Rankin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8659786581993103,
            "question": "Who directed the film _The Last Unicorn_?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.645051896572113,
            "question": "Is _The Last Unicorn_ a popular film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.526799201965332,
            "question": "What genre might the film _The Last Unicorn_ belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5020913481712341,
            "question": "Is _The Last Unicorn_ a live-action or animated film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4531782269477844,
            "question": "What is the subject matter of _The Last Unicorn_?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4410824775695801,
            "question": "When was _The Last Unicorn_ released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4401443898677826,
            "question": "What type of work did Arthur Rankin create?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arthur Rankin directed the film _The Last Unicorn_.",
            "html": "yago_11725_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was _The Last Unicorn_ released?",
            "html": "yago_11725_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the subject matter of _The Last Unicorn_?",
            "html": "yago_11725_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is _The Last Unicorn_ a live-action or animated film?",
            "html": "yago_11725_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11725_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11725_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11725_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11725_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11725_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11725_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11725_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11725_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11725_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11725_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information, I can evaluate the triple as follows:\n\n* \"Arthur Rankin directed the film _The Last Unicorn_.\"\n* The documents mention that \"The Last Unicorn is a 1982 Japanese-American animated film about a unicorn who... was directed and produced by Arthur Rankin, Jr. and Jules Bass.\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_11725/re-ranker-msmarco/61.txt)\n* The documents also mention that \"The Last Unicorn is a 1982 Japanese animated fantasy film directed & produced by Arthur Rankin, Jr. and Jules Bass...\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_11725/re-ranker-msmarco/7.txt)\n* The documents mention that \"Directed by Jules Bass & Arthur Rankin, Jr.\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_11725/re-ranker-msmarco/36.txt)\n\nAll the documents confirm that Arthur Rankin directed the film _The Last Unicorn_. Therefore:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that \"The Last Unicorn\" was directed by Arthur Rankin Jr. and Jules Bass."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}